popmyip.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | popmyip.com

**Privacy policy**

Jan, 2012 

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the popmyip.com's website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive services. 

Examples of personal information collected at these pages are: Name, Email address, Phone number, Friend's e-mail addresses (Tell-A-Friend) and Computer network information 

**Cookies:**

To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages may use "cookies." We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. 

**The Way We Use Information:**

We do not share this information with outside parties, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. If you have registered for one of our services and have thereby granted us permission to use your information, your sole recourse in prohibiting use of your information will be to cancel your registration and terminate your license. In any case, termination will be governed by the license agreement.

  **Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information. 

**Third-Party Websites**

This website may provide links to third-party websites. Any such links are provided solely as a convenience to you. popmyip.com has no control over these websites or their content and does not assume any responsibility or liability for these websites. popmyip.com does not endorse or make any representations about these websites, or any information, materials, or products found thereon. If you access any of the third-party websites linked on this Web site, you do so at your own risk.
